Contact

gabriellaychan@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/gaby-chan (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Leadership Customer Service Public Relations

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

Honors-Awards

Board of Trustees Community Service Award

Gaby Chan

Product Designer at Gather Town | UW MHCI+D

San Francisco Bay Area

Summary

I'm a product designer that recently graduated with a Masters in Human-Computer Interaction and Design. I strive to make delightful experiences that resonate with their audience by tailoring products to embody the core values they promote. I hope to shape how emerging technologies are being embedded into our lives while being cognizant of how the diversity of the human experience informs its design.

Experience

Gather Town
Product Designer
January 2021 - Present (5 months)

Omou Learning Lead Product Designer July 2019 - Present (1 year 11 months)

Digital learning space for tutoring centers to connect their student, parent, and teacher communities.

- Managing a product feature team to launch a tutoring management platform. Working on course registration, payments, and attendance tracking features.
- Established methods and review processes to improve the design team's workflow and design handoff to developers.
- Built and documented a design component library for the design system.
- · Involved in product planning and strategy with the product manager.

gabychan.com
Freelance Designer - gabychan.com
September 2017 - December 2020 (3 years 4 months)
Greater Los Angeles Area

- Produce personalized branding and promotional graphics for social media
- · Communicate with client to discuss the goals for their brand

 Clients include music artists, content creators, startups, and school affiliated organizations

Kloa

UX Design Consultant June 2020 - September 2020 (4 months)

Seattle, Washington, United States

- Worked on a mobile content sharing platform by a UW tech incubator startup.
- Identified design opportunities from user and market research, and drafted wireframes of early design concepts.

Fulcrum Labs
Product Design Intern
June 2018 - September 2018 (4 months)
Greater Los Angeles Area

- Researched learning behavior to provide input on improving Fulcrum's platform
- Proposed a product goal and developed the idea through an agile design process
- Provided recommendations for Fulcrum's marketing website by utilizing research and data analytics to improve visitor engagement
- Designed graphics for website/email marketing content

University of California, Los Angeles Office Assistant & Graphic Designer April 2017 - June 2018 (1 year 3 months) Greater Los Angeles Area

• Designed original print and web graphics for large scale events, merchandise.

and announcements on social media platforms

 Performed administrative tasks including scheduling, answering phone calls, data entry, running errands, and managing the Facebook page

Brighter Future Learning Center Classroom Assistant September 2014 - September 2016 (2 years 1 month) San Jose, CA

- Served as a classroom assistant for an academic after-school program
- Supervised groups of 20-30 students and provided support to students in need of assistance on curriculum

- Implemented a system to track student progress and took steps to ensure academic progress is where it should be
- Enforced classroom rules firmly, fairly, and consistently while maintaining a pleasant learning environment

The Tech Museum of Innovation
Marketing Intern
September 2015 - June 2016 (10 months)
San Jose, CA

- Engaged in a range of activities from museum marketing/PR events to writing compelling marketing copy
- Created content for social media accounts, updated event calendars and transcribed interviews and news broadcasts
- Performed office duties such as mailing, copying/faxing, and data entry

Education

University of Washington, Master of Human-Computer Interaction + Design

Master's degree, Human Computer Interaction + Design · (2019 - 2020)

University of California, Los Angeles

Bachelor's degree, Communication Studies B.A. and Digital Humanities Minor · (2018)

Lynbrook High School (2014)